
{
  "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "Bilbo is celebrating wich birthday at the begining of the first part of the Fellowship of the ring?",
        "answers":["101", "100", "111"],
        "correctAnswer": "111",
        "difficultyLevel": "Expert",
        "description": "111"
      },
      {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "How are Merry and Pippin related?",
        "answers":["They are first cousins", "They are brothers", "They are second cousins"],
        "correctAnswer": "They are first cousins",
        "difficultyLevel": "Expert",
        "description": "They are first cousins"
      },
      {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "What is Gollum’s name for the Sun?",
        "answers":["Yellow Face", "My precious"],
        "correctAnswer": "Yellow Face",
        "difficultyLevel": "Expert",
        "description": "Yellow Face"
      },
      {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "Gollum killed his brother for the one ring. What was his brother’s name?",
        "answers":["Deagol", "Pippin", "Diagol"],
        "correctAnswer": "Deagol",
        "difficultyLevel": "Expert",
        "description": "Deagol"
      },
      {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "How does Farmer Maggot keep people of his farm?",
        "answers":["A pack of trained dogs", "Fence"],
        "correctAnswer": "A pack of trained dogs",
        "difficultyLevel": "Expert",
        "description": "A pack of trained dogs"
      },
      {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "What river runs along the eastern border of the Shire?",
        "answers":["River Anduin", "The Brandywine"],
        "correctAnswer": "The Brandywine",
        "difficultyLevel": "Expert",
        "description": "The Brandywine"
      },
      {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "What kind of creatures are the spawns of Ungoliant?",
        "answers":["Giant spiders", "Crebain - crow-like birds"],
        "correctAnswer": "Giant spiders",
        "difficultyLevel": "Expert",
        "description": "Giant spiders"
      },
      {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "What are the Morgul-wounds?",
        "answers":["Wounds inflicted by the Nazgûl", "Wounds inflicted by Uruk-hai"],
        "correctAnswer": "Wounds inflicted by the Nazgûl",
        "difficultyLevel": "Expert",
        "description": "Wounds inflicted by the Nazgûl"
      },
      {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "What are the Palantíri and how many are there?",
        "answers":["3 powerful rings given to the Elves","7 seeing stones","3 jewels made by Fëanor"],
        "correctAnswer": "7 seeing stones",
        "difficultyLevel": "Expert",
        "description": "7 seeing stones"
      },
      {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "What was the name of Gandalf’s sword?",
        "answers":["Andúril","Glamdring"],
        "correctAnswer": "Glamdring",
        "difficultyLevel": "Expert",
        "description": "Glamdring"
      },
      {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "What is the first voice we hear in The Fellowship of the Ring?",
        "answers":["Galadriel", "Frodo", "Arwen"],
        "correctAnswer": "Galadriel",
        "difficultyLevel": "Expert",
        "description": "Galadriel"
      }
  ]
}
